Good morning.
(groaning)
(atmospheric music)
So which one of the
two are you right now?
Hey wait. Aren't you...
Satoru Gojou.
I'm head of the
first-years at Jujutsu Tech.
Jujutsu?
Fushiguro!
Where is he-
-(ropes tensing)
-Huh?
(distressing music)
What the hell is this?
I wouldn't be worrying
about others right now...
Yuuji Itadori.
(gasps)
You see, it's been decided
that you're to be
secretly executed.
(Opening Theme Music)
(singing in Japanese)
(phone ringing)
[Nurse] Sugisawa Hospital.
This is Yuuji Itadori.
I just called earlier.
Yes.
I'm sorry to
keep calling, but...
how's my grandpa doing?
[Nurse] Huh? I thought
they already told you.
Oh, never mind.
Just hold on a minute.
I'll go find out myself.
(soft guitar music)
Mister Itadori never
uses his call button.
It's kinda scary
that he doesn't.
[Nurse] Mister
Itadori, you have a call.
It's your grandson again,
asking if you want
him to bring you any-
Leave me alone!!
Tell him not to come here!
-(gasps)
-He should go to his club!
Go to his club!
[Nurse] I, uh...
I guess you probably heard that.
So what type club
are you in, Yuuji?
Yeah. I heard.
Thanks a lot.
(footsteps)
(dog barking)
(sirens)
They're keeping a
cursed object here,
in a place like this?
Could they be any more stupid?
(hutch door creaking)
Huh?
(groans)
There's nothing here.
[Satoru Gojou] Huh?
The Stevenson hutch is empty.
[Satoru] For real?
That's hilarious!
Maybe it took a
nighttime stroll.
I'm going to punch you.
[Satoru] Well, no going
home until it's recovered, okay?
(call disconnects)
I'm seriously
going to punch him.
(chattering)
Ready to go? What do you say?
Sasaki?
(grunts)
Iguchi?
Okay...
go!
Spirit gods, spirit gods,
which creature is the council
president barely weaker than?
(gasps)
[All Three] Ku..
ri...
o... ne.
-A sea angel's tougher?
-(laughing)
Occult club!
Hey!
Plankton president. What's up?
(slams)
As you were previously informed,
a research club
with no real activities
must forfeit its club room.
So vacate now!
You really ought
to be more careful
not to underestimate
our members, President.
(slams)
And what is that?
You know about the
school's rugby field
being closed off, don't you?
[School President] Yes.
Some of the
students who got sick
actually had to be hospitalized.
And so you don't
find that alarming?
We're talking about some
tough rugby players here!
The players said that,
just before they
started feeling sick...
(bong)
(gasps)
they heard mysterious
sounds and voices
coming from the field!
And then we found this
newspaper article from 30 years ago.
It talks about the disappearance
of a certain Mister Yoshida,
who worked for the
construction company.
It says he was last sighted here
at Sugisawa Third High
School during its construction.
(groans)
Yoshida was struggling
to make ends meet,
so he turned to loan sharks,
and those organizations
were after him!
Which means the whole
mysterious disaster at the rugby field
was caused by the
vengeful spirit of Yoshida,
whose body is buried there!
No, actually it was just ticks.
(light percussive music)
Hard ticks, to be exact.
Large blood-sucking bugs.
If one bites you and
infects you with SFTS,
it can be fatal, so
you have to be careful.
So what if it was ticks?
The occult club is trying
to uncover occult activity
so it's still a valid
activity report!
This is not some
kind of kids' game!
Besides the biggest
problem is you, Yuuji Itadori!
You're registered with track
and field, not the occult club!
So this club doesn't even
have the three members
required to be a club!
Uh...
You did that?
But I...
I'm sure I wrote "occult club"!
I'm the one who changed it.
Coach Takagi? What for?
Because! The track and
field team needs you on it!
[School President] So
says the only teacher
more problematic
than the students.
How many times
do I have to tell you
I'm not joining the team?
-You are.
-No I'm not!
However I'm not some demon.
So if you can defeat me I'll
excuse you from the team.
And we'll settle this fair
and square by competing!
That'll work! You've got a deal!
-Yay!
[School President]
How fair and square is it
to re-write a student's
club application?
(birds whistling)
[Fushiguro] What's
with this rugby field?
(gurgling)
Is there a dead body
buried here or something?
Even if there is, I'm
surprised to see a cursed spirit
this high-level here.
That looks like a
grade-two curse.
Must be the influence
of that cursed object.
(growling)
Damn. Its presence is
too strong to pin down.
It feels like it's close by,
but it could
actually be far away.
This special-grade cursed
object's a serious pain.
Who could have moved
it? And where is it now?
[Male Student] Hey,
come here, check this out!
Coach Takagi is taking on
Itadori from West Middle!
[Male Student] Wow, what
are they competing for?
[Takagi] Yeah!
(grunt)
14 meters!
-(victorious music)
-(grunting)
(applause and cheering)
[Man] Wow,
Takagi's still got it!
Wow, is he famous or something?
It's just a rumor, but
I heard that he beat
all the stages of
"Ninja Warrior"
and that he's the
reincarnation of Mirko Cro Cop.
[Sasaki] But Mirko's
not even dead yet.
He earned the nickname
"Tiger of West Middle."
That's lame.
Hey, so can I throw
it however I want?
Mm-hm!
For this challenge you can
throw however you want.
After all, I know this
event isn't your strong suit.
You've probably
never even really been...
(crash)
Uh...
about 30 meters, I guess.
(crowd gasps)
Yes! I crushed it!
Kinda more gorilla than tiger.
He threw that like a pitcher!
You'd do really well on
a sports team, Itadori.
(crowd chattering)
Don't force yourself to
stay in our occult club.
Huh?
Really?
But even though
you love scary stuff
without me you could
never go to haunted places!
But we like being scared.
School rules are I
have to be in some club.
And I could never keep this up.
You don't have to do anything!
You can be a ghost member!
After all we're the occult club!
(chuckles)
Yeah I did say that.
Besides, I want to be
able to go home by 6:00.
So if you two
don't mind I'll stay.
I really like being in your
club. It has a great vibe.
Well in that case we're
happy to have you back.
Yeah.
(laughing)
[Fushiguro] That
guy's incredible.
He pulled off that shot
without using any cursed energy.
I wonder if he's like Zen'in.
Whoa! It's already
half past four!
Later Coach! Got stuff to do!
(hollers)
(flashing)
(gasp)
The presence of a cursed object!
Hey hold it!
How is he that fast?
I heard he can run the
50 meters in three seconds.
Faster than my car!
(gentle guitar music)
I told you not to come!
And stop bringing
flowers with you every time!
[Yuuji] You always say that.
But you know
these aren't for you.
They're for the nurses.
All the more reason not to!
What's happening
with your school club?
Why aren't you at your club?
[Yuuji] Oh, chill out, Grandpa.
The club meeting
was over hours ago.
If I didn't have extra time,
I wouldn't be visiting you.
Good!
Now, listen to me since
I've got free time too.
[Yuuji] Not interested.
Listen anyway, I've
got some things
I want to say before
I reach the end.
It's about your parents and
-I want you to- -Come on!
I told you, I'm not interested.
Grandpa, please, could
you please stop trying to act
all cool before you die?
Every man has the
right to try to go out
with a little style.
Get a clue, you
useless grandson!
Quit all your complaining.
You don't have to
put on a show for me.
(scoffs)
You've had it too easy.
Yuuji...
[Yuuji] Hm?
[Grandpa] You're a strong
kid, so try to help others.
Save the people you can,
even if it's only
those closest to you.
It's okay if you lose your way,
and don't worry about
whether they'll thank you or not.
Just save as many as you can,
even if you can only save one.
When you die, you should
be surrounded by people.
Don't end up like me.
[Yuuji] Grandpa?
(phone beeping)
Yes? What can I do for you?
Are you there?
Mister Itadori!
(sniffling)
Hello, are you there?
[Yuuji] My grandpa...
is dead.
There. That's all the
paperwork we need from you.
[Yuuji] Yeah. Thanks
for helping me.
Are you sure you're
going to be okay?
Well, I...
I've never done this before
so it doesn't feel real yet.
But then I know
Grandpa would snap at me
if he saw me moping
around like this.
So I'll just have to
laugh as I roast him!
[Nurse] Be respectful.
[Man] Yuuji Itadori?
-Huh?
-Hm?
I'm Fushiguro from Jujutsu Tech.
I'd like to have a
word with you. Now.
[Yuuji] Uh, I'm in
mourning right now.
I understand,
but this can't wait.
The cursed object you
possess is very dangerous.
I need you to hand it over.
[Yuuji] Cursed object?
[Fushiguro] This.
Oh, yeah, that!
Yeah, I found that.
I didn't think much of it.
But my friends
were totally into it.
What's dangerous about it?
[Fushiguro] Every year
there are more than 10,000
unexplained deaths and
missing persons in Japan.
And most of those
are the result of curses.
From curses?
I don't care whether you
believe in them or not,
the fact is they exist.
Just listen.
Large pools of negative
energy form easily
in schools,
hospitals, and so on.
Hardship, regret, shame.
These emotions of mankind
become the source of curses.
That's why most schools
secretly keep a cursed object
to serve as a
protective talisman.
Just like the one you
and your friends found.
If it protects us, then
shouldn't we be grateful for it?
[Fushiguro] Just let me finish!
(grumbles)
A cursed object needs
to be incredibly evil
to keep lesser evil curses away.
But its protection
isn't permanent.
The problem is that their
seals weaken over time
and then they serve
as a lure to attract
and strengthen other curses.
The object you found
is a dangerous one,
classified as special-grade.
Now hand it over
before people start dying.
Agh! I already told you
that I don't have it anymore.
Here's the box.
It's empty!
I've just been following
a trace left by the object.
Hold it!
Where is it?
Knock it off!
You see Mm friends
were planning to...
To do what?
Well they were
saying let's open it up
to see what's inside tonight.
-Uh...
-(gasps)
Why? Is that bad?
It's way worse than bad.
Your friends are going to die.
I can't get it open.
Did we really need to sneak
into the building for this?
I'm gonna go turn on the light.
No don't! We need
some atmosphere!
Enjoying the thrill is
part of occult club isn't it?
It's not like anything's
going to happen here anyway.
(wrapping peels) (gasps)
Hey!
(mysterious music)
[Iguchi] Whoa, a human finger!
Is it real?
(gasps)
You think...
-(boom)
-(screams)
What's going on?
(voice trembling)
(snarling)
[Yuuji] Are talismans
that easy to open up?
No, it's impossible for
those without cursed energy.
Normally.
(sighs)
Go right here! Shortcut!
[Fushiguro] This time the
object itself is too strong!
And the seal is ancient. It
might as well be plain paper!
[Yuuji] I still don't get
all this stuff about curses!
[Fushiguro] Is that the
building? Where are they?
Fourth floor!
(grunts)
(intense music)
Whoa, what is this pressure?
I'll handle this.
Oh no way! I'm coming!
I may not know those
two that well, but...
but they're friends!
I have to help!
You're staying here.
(eerie music)
(whimpering)
(snarling)
[Monster] What time is it?
Just what is that thing?
[Iguchi] Sasaki?
-(gasp)
-Oh, Iguchi! Thank goodness!
Where have you bee-
Help me!
(choking)
(voice trembling)
What time is it?
(screams)
The curse has been unleashed!
Its presence is everywhere!
(panting)
(snarling)
Out of my way!
Demon Dogs!
(intense music)
(howling)
Eat it, boy!
Am I really just
gonna sit here and wait
because he told me to?
What the hell am I so afraid of?
Your friends are going to die.
[Yuuji] He was right.
I can sense death
all the way out here.
I'm afraid of dying.
Was I afraid of it before?
It didn't feel like I was.
I didn't cry because
I was scared.
I just felt a little sad.
But my grandpa's death
and the death I'm facing now...
How are they any different?
[Grandpa] You're a strong
kid, so try to help others.
(whimpering)
(blasting)
The curses are growing
in number! They're close!
(snarling)
There you are.
[Yuuji] Grandpa was crabby,
short-tempered and stubborn!
No one but me
ever even visited him!
"Don't end up like me,"
huh? Well, no chance of that!
[Fushiguro] Damn!
Is it trying to swallow her
along with the cursed object?
(moans)
I'm not gonna make it!
(dramatic music)
(confused mumble)
(glass shattering)
(grunting)
Itadori!!
I think you had a
proper death, Grandpa!
(grunting)
But this kind of a death...
is just wrong!
(snarling)
(moaning)
So this is a curse? Not
what I was expecting.
(groans)
I should be asking what
you're doing here but good job.
You're pretty smug, aren't you?
So, just curious,
what are those things
munching on the curse?
My shikigami. Wait,
you can see them?
Normally a curse can't be seen.
Not unless you're
on the verge of death
or in special places like this.
Yeah, that makes sense.
I've never seen ghosts or
weird stuff like this before.
Huh. But you're
not scared though?
I was. I mean for
a little while there.
But then I thought,
everybody's gonna die.
Huh?
So I want to make sure
that the people I know
all have a chance
at a proper death.
Not that I really understand it.
Whoa!
This it?
Yeah, the cursed object,
Ryoumen Sukuna's finger.
It's a miracle that
thing didn't swallow it.
Why would anything
eat this? Is it good?
Don't be dense.
You'd eat it to gain
stronger cursed energy.
Now hand it over,
it's dangerous.
Fine, here.
(gasps)
(snarling)
Run!
(crash)
(grunting)
(electricity crackling)
(growling)
Damn!
Nue!
(grunting)
(groaning)
(roars)
(blast)
(dramatic music)
(grunting)
(roaring)
Damn it!
Why can't I think straight?
Itadori!
Your only chance is to
take those two and run for it!
(roars)
You're in big trouble yourself!
(grunting)
(yells)
Only a curse can beat a curse!
You cannot defeat this!
Is that your idea of a pep talk?
At this rate, we're
both gonna die!
If I quit now I'll be having
this nightmare for weeks!
Besides...
(snarling)
I know what I have to do!
[Grandpa] Try to help others.
I'm living with a rotten
curse of my own already!
(grunts)
(intense music)
You idiot! Throw it down to
me or you'll both get eaten!
(grunting)
(growling)
[Yuuji] Why would
anything eat this? Is it good?
[Fushiguro] Don't be dense.
You'd eat it to gain
stronger cursed energy.
(straining)
There's a way I
can save everyone!
I just need to have my
own cursed energy. don't I?
Don't do it.
Don't do it!
(swallowing)
Ryoumen Sukuna's finger!
That's a special-grade
cursed object!
It's a deadly poison!
He'll die for sure!
But, there is a chance, a
one-in-a-million chance
(boom)
(grunts)
(roaring)
(blast)
(gasp)
(cackling)
[Yuuji] I knew it! The
light feels best in the flesh!
[Fushiguro] This is the worst,
a one-in-a-million-chance,
worst-case scenario!
The special-grade cursed
object has incarnated!
Cursed flesh is so boring!
So now where are the
people? The women?
What a wonderful
era to be reawakened!
Women and children are
crawling everywhere like maggots!
How marvelous!
It'll be a massacre!
(cackling)
(confused mumbling)
[Yuuji] What do you think
you're doing with my body?
Give it back!
Hey, wait. How
are you doing that?
Well, it's my body!
Wait...
He's suppressing me?
[Fushiguro] Stay
right where you are!
You're no longer human!
Huh?
Under Jujutsu regulation....
Yuuji Itadori...
by law I will now
exorcize you...
as a curse!
(dramatic music)